{"showBridgeTasks":true,"taskHeader":"Deck \u0026 Porch Repair Services","categoryPerformanceTest":true,"scrollyPathPageBase":"","providedPostalCode":"","hideAllSemIcons":false,"scrolly_persistedParams":{},"addressId":null,"AdobeFlickerMgmtOn":false,"SCROLLY_FILTER_NON_REQUIRED_33367":false,"headerBranding":{"src":"/images/consumer/cobranding/HA.svg","name":"ha"},"__cache./api/resource/task/40023/?r_version=1":{"taskOid":40023,"taskName":"Deck or Porch - Repair","taskDescription":"Repair a Deck or Porch","xmTaskDescriptor":"Deck \u0026 Porch Repair Services","matchable":false,"profileable":true,"esScore":0.0,"defaultCostGuideTaskId":290,"active":true,"taskKeywords":"deck porch wood front screen","textMessagingName":"Repair Deck","rolloverLongDesc":"Includes deck surfaces, railings \u0026 associated stairs \u0026 landings.  Could be made of redwood, pine, treated pine, vinyl or any of a variety of artificial woods.","rolloverShortDesc":"Deck materials include wood, vinyl \u0026 other artificial woods.","sectorId":"HS","metaDescription":"Find local contractors to Repair a Deck or Porch.  HomeAdvisor will connect you with prescreened and customer-rated contractors in your area","htmlTitle":"Deck Repair Contractors \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Porch Repair","contentDescription":null,"pwcId":17,"acceptGoal":3,"multiZip":false,"preMatchTypeId":0,"bridgeTaskOid":39794,"bridgeTaskText":"Note: If your repair is not very complex, or you have a variety of small projects, please ","bridgeTaskLinkText":"request a Handyman.","bridgeTaskLinkId":1437,"bridgeTaskActive":"Y","xmName":"Deck or Porch Repair","redirectToTaskOid":-1,"spDisplayName":"Deck or Porch - Repair","xmHeaderDescriptor":"Describe Your Deck or Porch Project","urlName":"Deck-or-Porch-Repair","taskConsiderationId":1,"siteVisible":true,"attributeMatchable":true,"htmlTitleTloc":"\u003cspcount\u003e Best Deck \u0026 Porch Repair Contractors - \u003ccity\u003e \u003cstatecode\u003e | Costs \u0026 Reviews","searchKeywords":"deck, porch, wood, frontporch, enclosure, pine, vinyl, redwood, railing, stairs, landing, hot tub","emcCategoryOid":-12017,"locationDisplayText":"What is the location of your project?","semLocationDisplayText":"To get started, enter the location of your project","commentsPromptText":"Please provide a short description of your project","primaryQuestionSetId":347,"locationSpecific":false,"commercial":false,"viewFirstParentTask":false},"entryPointId":0,"matchingSourceId":2,"scrollyProgressBarTest":false,"isMobile":false,"consumer":{"entityId":0},"affiliateCode":"sm_def_sto","twoPageSubmit":true,"sar":true,"scrolly_customDefaults":["50001_10002","8152_10002","30001_10002","160804_10002","20001_10002","160807_10002","160805_10002","502713_10002","160810_6938","8373_67562","8374_67566"],"entityId":0,"sessionId":"1564368210609pwspr010376737CC5AE756748174EA7F763C984D.pwspr010-1","shouldShowTasks":true,"KNOWN_USER_SCROLLY_TEST_SITE_33390":"ctrl","semThreeIcons":false,"__cache./api/resource/task/interview/40023/":{"taskOID":40023,"originalTaskOID":40023,"setID":347,"interviewType":"TASK_INTERVIEW","questions":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":695,"questionDisplayText":"Nature of the repair","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of repair or maintenance do you need for your deck?  (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1842,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Deck is unstable","answerDisplayText":"Deck is unstable","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2396,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Faulty or broken stairs/railing","answerDisplayText":"Faulty or broken stairs/railing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6026,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Stairs/Railings not to code","answerDisplayText":"Stairs/Railings not to code","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3662,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Loose decking or stairs","answerDisplayText":"Loose decking or stairs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1945,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Discolored/Mildewed decking","answerDisplayText":"Discolored/Mildewed decking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5426,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Rotted decking or stairs","answerDisplayText":"Rotted decking or stairs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6921,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Waterproofing","answerDisplayText":"Waterproofing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":826,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Arbor/Pergola is damaged","answerDisplayText":"Arbor/Pergola is damaged","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5049,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Re-staining","answerDisplayText":"Re-staining","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":696,"questionDisplayText":"Current deck material","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is your deck made of?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5089,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Redwood","answerDisplayText":"Redwood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1281,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Cedar","answerDisplayText":"Cedar","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4904,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Pressure-treated pine","answerDisplayText":"Pressure-treated pine","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1542,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Composite/Synthetic materials","answerDisplayText":"Composite/Synthetic materials","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6696,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Vinyl","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":16749,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}],"questionElements":[{"questionID":8152,"questionDisplayText":"Is this an emergency?","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"Is this an emergency?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":true,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":695,"questionDisplayText":"Nature of the repair","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":2,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What kind of repair or maintenance do you need for your deck?  (Select all that apply)","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":1842,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Deck is unstable","answerDisplayText":"Deck is unstable","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2396,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Faulty or broken stairs/railing","answerDisplayText":"Faulty or broken stairs/railing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6026,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Stairs/Railings not to code","answerDisplayText":"Stairs/Railings not to code","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3662,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Loose decking or stairs","answerDisplayText":"Loose decking or stairs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1945,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Discolored/Mildewed decking","answerDisplayText":"Discolored/Mildewed decking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5426,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Rotted decking or stairs","answerDisplayText":"Rotted decking or stairs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6921,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Waterproofing","answerDisplayText":"Waterproofing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":826,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Arbor/Pergola is damaged","answerDisplayText":"Arbor/Pergola is damaged","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5049,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Re-staining","answerDisplayText":"Re-staining","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":1842,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Deck is unstable","answerDisplayText":"Deck is unstable","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":2396,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Faulty or broken stairs/railing","answerDisplayText":"Faulty or broken stairs/railing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6026,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Stairs/Railings not to code","answerDisplayText":"Stairs/Railings not to code","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":3662,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Loose decking or stairs","answerDisplayText":"Loose decking or stairs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1945,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Discolored/Mildewed decking","answerDisplayText":"Discolored/Mildewed decking","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5426,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Rotted decking or stairs","answerDisplayText":"Rotted decking or stairs","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6921,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Waterproofing","answerDisplayText":"Waterproofing","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":826,"answerDisplaySequence":8,"answerText":"Arbor/Pergola is damaged","answerDisplayText":"Arbor/Pergola is damaged","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":5049,"answerDisplaySequence":9,"answerText":"Re-staining","answerDisplayText":"Re-staining","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":10,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"checkbox","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":696,"questionDisplayText":"Current deck material","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":1,"questionText":"What is your deck made of?","shortQuestionText":"","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5089,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Redwood","answerDisplayText":"Redwood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1281,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Cedar","answerDisplayText":"Cedar","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4904,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Pressure-treated pine","answerDisplayText":"Pressure-treated pine","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1542,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Composite/Synthetic materials","answerDisplayText":"Composite/Synthetic materials","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6696,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Vinyl","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":16749,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5089,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Redwood","answerDisplayText":"Redwood","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1281,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Cedar","answerDisplayText":"Cedar","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4904,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"Pressure-treated pine","answerDisplayText":"Pressure-treated pine","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":1542,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"Composite/Synthetic materials","answerDisplayText":"Composite/Synthetic materials","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":6696,"answerDisplaySequence":5,"answerText":"Vinyl","answerDisplayText":"Vinyl","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4444,"answerDisplaySequence":6,"answerText":"Other","answerDisplayText":"Other","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":16749,"answerDisplaySequence":7,"answerText":"Don't know","answerDisplayText":"Don't know","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":90000,"questionDisplayText":"Request Stage","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":1,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Choose the appropriate status for this project:","shortQuestionText":"Project Status:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":5052,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Ready to Hire","answerDisplayText":"Ready to Hire","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":4702,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","answerDisplayText":"Planning \u0026 Budgeting","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":80000,"questionDisplayText":"Desired Completion Date","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":3,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"When would you like this request to be completed?","shortQuestionText":"To be completed in:","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":true,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":11149,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Timing is flexible","answerDisplayText":"Timing is flexible","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11150,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"Within 1 week","answerDisplayText":"Within 1 week","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11151,"answerDisplaySequence":3,"answerText":"1 - 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"1 - 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":11152,"answerDisplaySequence":4,"answerText":"More than 2 weeks","answerDisplayText":"More than 2 weeks","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"select","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":50001,"questionDisplayText":"Covered by Insurance","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":4,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Is this request covered by an insurance claim?","shortQuestionText":"Covered by an insurance claim?","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]},{"questionID":501504,"questionDisplayText":"Property Owner","displayToSP":true,"questionDisplaySequence":6,"pageNumber":2,"questionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","shortQuestionText":"Are you the owner or authorized to make property changes? ","parentQuestionID":0,"parentAnswerID":0,"parentQuestionText":"","required":false,"glossaryTerm":false,"defaultAnswer":-9999,"active":true,"attributeMatch":false,"answers":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}],"answerElements":[{"answerID":10001,"answerDisplaySequence":1,"answerText":"Yes","answerDisplayText":"Yes","active":true,"defaultAnswer":true,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]},{"answerID":10002,"answerDisplaySequence":2,"answerText":"No","answerDisplayText":"No","active":true,"defaultAnswer":false,"presentationType":"radio","childQuestions":[]}]}]},"isCookielessUser":true}